A Guide to the David Rockefeller papers, Photographic collections, Numbered Albums FA1316
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Bangkok, Thailand Trip, 1995 (Box 46)
  DR trip to Bangkok, Thailand. Meeting with Queen Sirikit at the Thai royal residence.
  24 images
- Bartlett's Island, Maine, Trip for Chase Manhattan Bank, 1980 December (Box 47)
  DR and PR hosted a group from Chase Bank (Chase BODSA) at their property on Bartlett's Island, Maine.
- B-Bar Ranch, JY Ranch Trips, 1997, 1999 (Box 48)
  DR and PR trips to B-Bar Ranch in Montana (1997), owned by friends, and JY Ranch in Jackson Hole, Wyoming (1999). Family and friends accompanied them to JY Ranch.
  52 images.
- Brooke Russell Astor Birthday Celebration, 2002 (Box 49)
  Celebration for Brooke Astor's 100th birthday, held at the Playhouse in Pocantico Hills, New York. Guests include DR, Laurance Rockefeller, Happy Rockefeller, Kofi Annan, Henry Kissinger, Morley Safer, and Barbra Walters. A CD of the photos is included in the album.
- Burma Trip, 2003 (Box 50)
  DR trip to Burma (Myanmar). He met with Aung San Suu Kyi, opposition leader and 1991 recipient of the Nobel Peace Prize. Images include many Buddhist sites, boat rides, and a balloon ride through the countryside.
  172 images
- Burma and Bhutan Trip, 2003 (Box 51)
  DR trip to Burma (Myanmar) and Bhutan. The Bhutan photos include various Buddhist sites, ceremonies, and crafts.
  77 images
- Caracas, Venezuela Trip, 1989, 1989 February (Box 52)
  DR trip to Caracas, Venezuela, to receive the medal for the Order of Don Andres Bello. Presented by President Carlos Andres Perez at the Palacio de Miraflores. Awarded for service to the arts.
  13 images.
- Caracas, Venezuela Trip, 1985, 1985 February (Box 53)
  DR trip for Chase Bank International Advisory Committee to Caracas, Venezuela. Part of Latin American trip that included Brazil, Ecuador, and Mexico. While in Caracas, DR stayed at the guest house of his friend Gustavo Cisneros. He visited with U.S. Ambassador George Landau, and he was presented with the Order of Francisco de Miranda by President Jaime Lusinchi at the Palacio de Miraflores. The award is for contributions to the sciences, to the progress of the country, or to the humanities.
- Turkey and Israel Trip with Council on Foreign Relations, 2000 (Box 54)
  DR trip with delegation from the Council on Foreign Relations to Turkey and Israel. DR was co-chair of the delegation. They met with Mustafa Bulent Ecevit, the prime minister of Turkey, and with Suleyman Demirel, the president of Turkey. They later visited with the Palestine legislative council.
  87 images.
- Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania, Carriage Rides, 1982 (Box 55)
  DR and PR visit the Hewitt family in Chadds Ford, PA, and take several carriage rides.
  11 images
- China Trip, 2001, Part 1 (Box 56)
  DR trip to China. Sites include temples, markets, mountains, sand dunes, a panda sanctuary, and the Great Wall.
  197 images.
- China Trip, 2001, Part 2 (Box 57)
  DR trip to China. Sites include mountain villages, river boat tour, dam construction, panda sanctuary.
- Chase Manhattan Bank Trip through Asia, 1983 (Box 58)
  DR trip as chair of the Chase International Advisory Committee to Taipei, Taiwan; Hong Kong; Bangkok, Thailand; Chiang Mai, Thailand; Jakarta, Indonesia; and Singapore. Images of meetings, receptions, musueums, villages, markets, temples, and an elephant ride.
  177 images.
- Chase Manhattan Bank Trip to Hong Kong, 1998 (Box 59)
  DR trip to Hong Kong with Chase Bank employees. Images include meetings, reception, and dinner.
  44 images.
- Chase Manhattan Bank Trip to Osaka, Japan, 1962; Black-and-white images. (Box 60)
  DR and PR trip to Osaka, Japan, as guests of Tokeo Terao, president of Daiway Bank Ltd. Images include a tour, a reception, and a performance at Mr. Terao's residence.
- Chase Manhattan Bank Outing to Pocantico Hills, 1951 May 26; Black-and-white images. (Box 61)
  DR hosted an an outing for the Chase Foreign Department officers at the Playhouse on the Rockefeller estate in Pocantico Hills, New York. Golfing, croquet, horseshoes, carriage rides, baseball. John D. Rockefeller 3rd attended.
- Colorado River Trip, Utah and Arizona, 1983 June (Box 62)
  DR and PR rafting trip on the Colorado River through Cataract Canyon, Utah, to Lake Powell, Arizona.
  128 images.
- Columbia University, Global Economic Development, Trip to La Romana, Dominican Republic, 2002; Some black-and-white images. (Box 63)
  DR trip to La Romana, Dominican Republic, for Columbia University-sponsored, multi-national gathering on the study of global economic development.
  59 images
- Construction of Jean Dubuffet sculpture, "Group of 4 Trees", 1970-1972; Black-and-white images. (Box 64)
  Images, plans, and drawings of design and construction of Jean Dubuffet's monumental sculpture for the Chase Manhattan Bank plaza, "Group of 4 Trees."
  45 images
- Consulate General of Mexico in New York, Award Ceremony, 1997 September 24 (Box 65)
  DR received the medal of the Mexican Order of the Aztec Eagle from the Mexican government at a ceremony held at the Americas Society in New York.
- Costa Rica Trip, 2005 (Box 66)
  DR trip to Costa Rica and possibly Guatemala. Scenery includes, plants, wildlife, and ruins.
- Colombier Guests, St. Bart's Property, 1962-1980; Image quality varies.; Some black-and-white images. (Box 67)
  Images of guests at DR's home, Colombier, on St. Bart's (Saint Barthelemy), in the Caribbean. Guests include Henry Kissinger, Nancy Kissinger, Winston Lord, Robert Douglass, Linda Douglass, and family members.
  61 images.
- Cuba and Mexico Trip for Council on Foreign Relations, 2001 February (Box 68)
  DR trip to Cuba and Mexico as part of Council on Foreign Relations delegation. They met with Cuban president Fidel Castro and Mexican president Vicente Fox.
  76 images
- David Kaiser, Baby Photos, 1970; Some black-and-white images. (Box 69)
  Baby photos of David Kaiser with mother, Neva, and father, Walter.
  32 images.
- Dinner for Dick and Ginny Voell, 1996 January 23 (Box 70)
  DR and PR hosted a dinner at their home on E. 65th Street in New York for Dick and Ginny Voell. Mr. Voell had served as President of the Rockefeller Group and was Chair of the Buisness Council for the United Nations. Richard Parsons attended.
  38 images.
- Dominican Republic Trip for Chase Manhattan Bank, 1981, 1981 July (Box 71)
  DR trip to Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic, to visit Chase branch and meet with country manager Philip Young. He also addressed a luncheon of the Dominican Chamber of Commerce.
  22 images.
- Donald Bryant Compilation Album of DR Family in Maine, 1985 (Box 72)
  Staff member Donald Bryant compiled this album of DR and PR with their children and grandchildren on a sailing vacation in Maine.
- DR and Peggy Western Trip, 1970 (Box 73)
  DR and PR trip with friends, probably to JY Ranch in Jackson Hole, Wyoming. Horseback riding and hiking.
  41 images.
- DR Farewell Party from U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 1998 (Box 74)
  Party held in the Rainbow Room at Rockefeller Center. DR served on the board of the U.S. Chamber of Commerce.
  25 images.
- Family Album, 1955-1961; Some black-and-white images.; Some blurry, faded, grainy images. (Box 75)
  Snapshots of family members mostly outdoors at various homes and vacation sites, with pets and farm animals, and with friends.
  64 images.
- Family Album, Playhouse, St. Bart's, Wyoming, Maine, 1980 (Box 76)
  Family snapshots at various gatherings. Locations include Colombier on St. Bart's, Jackson Hole in Wyoming, Seal Harbor in Maine, and (in July) the Playhouse in Pocantico Hills, New York.
  62 images.
- James Ford Family Compilation Album, 2002-2013 (Box 77)
  Album of family of DR staff member James Ford. Includes family pictures, wedding to Rebeca Ford, vacations, christenings, and other gatherings with DR.
  Material restricted from access until January 1, 2025.
- Four Winds, Columbia County, New York Compilation Album, 2000-2009 (Box 78)
  Compilation of images of the farm Four Winds and surrounding property in upstate New York, plus family gatherings with DR.
  157 images.
- Four Winds, Columbia County, New York Album, 2006 (Box 79)
  Images of the farm, herds, property, interior, and furnishings of DR's home Four Winds in upstate, Columbia County, New York.
- France Canal Cruise on Princess Barge, 1983 July (Box 80)
  DR and PR joined friends on the Princess barge along the Marne canal in France. They took walking and biking excursions along the way.
  77 images.
- Galapagos Islands, Ecuador Trip, February 1985, 1985 February; Some black-and-white images. (Box 81)
  DR trip for Chase Bank International Advisory Committee to the Galapagos Islands, Ecuador. Part of Latin American trip that included Brazil, Venezuela, and Mexico. While in the Galapagos, DR and PR toured several islands and photographed the landscape, plants, and animals.
  While in Quito, DR met with President Leon Febres Cordero, who presented DR with La Orden National al Merito.
  117 images.
- Galapagos Islands, Ecuador Trip 1987 (Box 82)
  Photo album from Martha Twitchell Muse of DR and PR's trip to the Galapagos Islands.
- Galapagos Islands, Ecuador Trip with Family, 1995-1996, 1995 Dec-1996 Jan (Box 83)
  DR and PR organized a trip to the Galapagos Islands for 23 family members.
  97 images.
- Germany Trip, 1933, Black-and-white images. Original album is fragile.; Some grainy images. (Box 84)
  DR travels through Germany, France, Austria, and Italy during college: Munchen, Weisbaden, Rottenbuch, Bavaria, Nuremberg, Stuttgart, Frankfort, Innsbruck, Tyrol, Verona, and Venice. Tours through castles, churches, villages, cities, gardens, rivers, estates, and mountains. Stays with Demutter family. Some images are purchased souvenirs.
  236 images.
  Restricted due to preservation concerns. Album is fragile. Permission required to access original album.
- Germany Exhibit of Leger and Picasso, 1972, Mostly black-and-white images. (Box 85)
  Album of art exhibit of Leger and Picasso works in Koln, Germany, sent to DR by Hans Gerlin. DR did not attend the exhibit.
  24 images.
- DR 90th Birthday Celebration with Office Staff at Room 5600, 2005 June (Box 86)
  The staff at DR's office at Room 5600 of 30 Rockefeller Plaza threw him a party at the office for his 90th birthday.
- Graneros, Chile Trip, 1991 (Box 87)
  DR and PR attended an Americas Society event in Chile.
  110 images.
- Guinea Trip, Chase Manhattan Bank, 1982 February; Black-and-white images. (Box 88)
  DR trip to Guinea, as part of 10-nation trip that also included Senegal, Ivory Coast, Nigeria, Cameroon, Gabon, Angola, Zimbabwe, Zambia, and Morocco for Chase International Advisory Committee. DR met with Ahmed Sekou Toure, the first president of the Republic of Guinea.
- Harvard Board of Overseers Dinner, Award for DR, 2008 April 25 (Box 89)
  DR received an award from the Committe on University Resources of the Harvard Board of Overseers. Presented by president Drew Faust and attended by former president Derek Bok.
  48 images.
- Harvard University, DR Center for Latin American Studies Album, 2007-2008; A few black-and-white images. (Box 90)
  Compilation album of students, faculty, and events of the David Rockefeller Center for Latin American Studies at Harvard University. Album compiled for DR's birthday in 2008.
  18 images.
- Hong Kong, Vietnam, China Trip, 1993 (Box 91)
  DR trip, possibly for Chase Bank International Advisory Committee.
  55 images.
- Luncheon for Felix Houphouet-Boigny, 1962 May (Box 92)
  DR and PR hosted a luncheon for Felix Houphouet-Boigny, President of the Cote d'Ivoire (Ivory Coast), and his family at their Pocantico Hills, New York, home. DR also took him to visit Chase Manhattan Bank headquarters in Manhattan.
- Hudson Pines and Playhouse, Pocantico Hills, 1998-2003, Some images are grainy. (Box 93)
  Compilation album of Hudson Pines, DR's home in Pocantico Hills, New York, and of the Playhouse on the Kykuit estate property. Images of family, friends, staff, exteriors, interiors, gardens, horse carriage rides, outdoor parties, and some artwork. Kofi Annan, Brooke Astor, Laurance Rockefeller, and Happy Rockefeller are included.
  147 images
- Hudson Pines and Playhouse, Pocantico Hills, Event for Museum of Modern Art, 2011, 2011 September 12; A few black-and-white images. (Box 94)
  DR hosted a dinner for the trustees of the Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) at his home, Hudson Pines, and the Playhouse on the Kykuit estate property in Pocantico Hills, New York. Attendees included MoMA president Glenn Lowry and president emerita Agnes Gund.
- Hudson Pines Compilation Album, 1944-1980s, Several black-and-white images.; Some images are blurry or faded. (Box 95)
  Compilation album of events and people at DR and PR's home Hudson Pines, in Pocantico Hills, New York. Family, friends, staff, grounds, gardens, animals.
- Hudson Pines and Kykuit Compilation Album, 1944-1997, Some black-and-white images.; Some images are grainy or blurry. (Box 96)
  Compilation album of events at DR and PR's home Hudson Pines, in Pocantico Hills, New York. Family, friends, staff, grounds, carriage and sleigh rides, gardens, animals, barns, livestock (cattle auction hosted by Hudson Pines Farms). Some images on Kykuit estate property as well.
  120 images.
- Hudson Pines Compilation Album, 2003, Some images are grainy/blurry. (Box 97)
  Compilation album of events at DR's Hudson Pines home and farm, in Pocantico Hills, New York. Mostly family and farm staff, with the grounds, gardens, animals, livestock, barns, greenhouses, horses, and some images on Kykuit estate property. A few images with Laurance Rockefeller.
  108 images.
- Hudson Pines Gardens, 2012, 2012 April (Box 98)
  Gardens and grounds in bloom at DR's home, Hudson Pines, in Pocantico Hills, New York.
  27 images.
- Hudson Pines Gardens, 1968, Color in images is faded. (Box 99)
- International House Compilation Album, 1925-1982; Black-and-white images. (Box 100)
  Images of International House students and DR at I House events over several decades, compiled in 1982. Guests include Eleanor Roosevelt, Dwight D. Eisenhower, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, and Henry Kissinger.
  35 images.
- Iran Trip, 1970, 1970 May; Black-and-white images. (Box 101)
  DR and PR trip to Iran as part of a larger trip, during which DR attended an Iran Investment Conference hosted by the government. Images are of a private tour arranged through the Deputy Minister of Economy, Hassan Ali Mehran.
- ITAM 60th Anniversary Celebration, 2006 (Box 102)
  The Instituto Tecnológico Autónomo de México (ITAM) in Mexico City celebrated its 60th anniversary and presented DR with an honorary degree to acknowledge his support of the research institution.
  59 images.
- Jamaica Trip, Part 1, 2013 (Box 103)
  DR trip to Jamaica with friends and associates
- Japan, Korea, JY Ranch Trips, 2003 (Box 104)
  DR trips with his family to Japan, Korea, and JY Ranch in Wyoming.
  76 images.
- Jerusalem, Israel Trip, Part 1, 1971 March 10; Black-and-white images. (Box 105)
  DR and PR attended the dedication of the Nelson A. Rockefeller Garden in East Jerusalem. The land was originally acquired by the Rockefeller Foundation in the 1920s for an archaeological museum.
- Jerusalem, Israel Trip, Part 2, 1971 March; Black-and-white images. (Box 106)
  PR and DR trip to Jerusalem, as part of a trip on behalf of Chase Manahattan Bank. They also visited Rome, Italy; Bahrain; Beirut, Lebanon; Ceylon (Sri Lanka); Indonesia; and Australia.
- JY Ranch Family Vacation, 1981, 1981 July (Box 107)
  DR and PR trip with family to JY Ranch in Wyoming. Hiking, sailing, fishing, horseback riding, wildlife, wildflowers, landscape, rodeo.
  145 images.
- JY Ranch Vacation; Maine Trip; Tarrytown, 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 108)
  Compilation album of DR and PR trip with friends to JY Ranch in Wyoming. Hiking, fishing, horseback riding, wildlife, wildflowers, landscape. Images of Pocantico Hills and New York harbor. Bee keeping. Ringing Point in Maine, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden, sailing.
- JY Ranch Vacation, St. Bart's Trip Compilation Album, 1957-1960s, Some black-and-white images.; Some faded and discolored images. (Box 109)
  Compilation album of DR and PR trips. JY Ranch in Wyoming, home in Maine. Mostly images of the construction of Colombier, their home on St. Bart's in the Caribbean, that was designed by DR's cousin Nelson Aldrich. Sailing, landscape, formal event.
  70 images.
- Kenya and Tanzania Trip, Part 1, 2000 (Box 110)
  DR trip to Kenya, followed by Tanzania. Wildlife safari in Kenya at the Shaba Game Preserve and possibly the Lake Nakuru national park. In Tanzania, they visited Serengeti National Park. Camel herders, farmers.
  218 images.
- Kenya and Tanzania Trip, Part 2, 2000 (Box 111)
  DR trip to Kenya, followed by Tanzania. Visit to Shaba Game Preserve in Kenya.
  180 images.
- Kenya, Tanzania, and Rwanda Trip, 2003, Several images are blurry/poor quality. (Box 112)
  DR trip to Kenya, Tanzania, and Rwanda. Tours in each country, wildlife, landscape, gorilla sanctuary.
- Henry Kissinger's 60th Birthday Celebration, 1983 May 23; Several black-and-white images. (Box 113)
  Celebration in honor of former Secretary of State Henry Kissinger on his 60th birthday. Hosted by Guido Goldman and held at the Hotel Pierre in Manhattan. Attendees included DR, former President Gerald Ford and Betty Ford, George Shultz, Ladybird Johnson, Katherine Graham, Happy Rockefeller, Helmut Schmidt, William Casey, and Brent Scowcroft.
- Dinner Hosted at Kykuit, June 1983, 1983 June 28 (Box 114)
  DR and PR hosted a dinner held at Kykuit in Pocantico Hills for the New York City Partnership.
- Kykuit Family Christmas Celebration, 1976, 1976 December 19 (Box 115)
  Nelson Rockefeller hosted the annual family Christmas celebration, a lunch held at Kykuit.
- Ladies Cruise, 2004 (Box 116)
  DR hosted a day on his boat as a thank-you for his staff in Maine.
- Libya and Egypt Trip for Council on Foreign Relations, 2005 April; Images are grainy or poor quality. (Box 117)
  DR trip to Libya and Egypt on behalf of the Council on Foreign Relations. Includes images from meetings, dinners, and sightseeing in both countries.
  208 images.
- Lord Roy Thomson's Luncheon for DR, Claridge's, London, 1968 October 17; Black-and-white images. (Box 118)
  Luncheon thrown for DR by Lord Roy Thomson at Claridge's of London during a trip for Chase Manhattan Bank to England, Germany, France, Italy, and Lebanon. Attendees at the lunch included family friend Lord Louis Mountbatten and Prime Minister Harold Wilson.
- Madrid, Spain Trip, 1983 April (Box 119)
  DR trip to Madrid, Spain, for a combined trip for Chase Bank's International Advisory Council and the Trilateral Commission. DR had an audience with King Juan Carlos de Borbon Gustavo, and later met with Prime Minister Felipe Gonzalez. Tours of the Prado, Plaza Mayor, and Museum of Contemporary Art. Friend Gustavo Cisneros joined DR on this trip.
- Maine Cruise, August 1977, 1977 August; A couple of black-and-white images. (Box 120)
  DR and PR vacation in Maine included a few days sailing with Rick and Christie Salomon near Bartlett's Island.
- Maine Sailing Album, 1972 (Box 121)
  DR sailing on Jack Tar off the coast of Maine. All images are on boats.
- Marshall Foundation Award Dinner, 1999 May 17 (Box 122)
  DR received an award from the George C. Marshall Foundation at an event held at the New York Public Library. The award honors a career of distinguished public service. Tom Brokaw attended, as did cadets from Virginia Military Academy (VMI).
- Memoirs Publication Event at Rockefeller University, 2003 October 22 (Box 123)
  Celebration of the publication of DR's "Memoirs" by Random House, held at Rockefeller University. Attended by family, friends, and staff plus past and present leaders of Rockefeller University and Rockefeller Foundation.
- Mexico Trip, 2004, 2004 March-April (Box 124)
  DR trip to Mexico. He visited Mexico City and Oaxaca. Tours of churches, markets, gardens, pyramids.
  90 images.
- Middlebury, Vermont Trip, 1974 (Box 125)
  DR and PR trip to Middlebury, Vermont, and tour of maple sugaring process in the snow.
- Miranda Kaiser and David Rockefeller Compilation Album, 1996-1999 (Box 126)
  David Rockefeller's granddaughter compiled this album of their extensive international travels together. Countries and territories included Austria, Canada, Finland, France, Hong Kong, India, Kazakhstan, Majorca, Peru, Russia, Spain, and Venezuela.
  34 images.
- Montana and Napa Valley, California Trip, 2002 July (Box 127)
  DR trip to Montana horse ranch and Napa Valley winery with family.
- Alaska Trip, 1993 (Box 128)
  104 images
  DR and PR boating vacation in Alaska. Guests include Robert Douglass, Linda Douglass, Marnie Pillsbury, Don Pillsbury, and Rick Fleishman
- British Columbia Trip, 1966 Summer (Box 129)
  DR and PR sailing trip in British Columbia with friends and family.
- DR and PR Family Album, 1985, 1985 August (Box 130)
  Compiled album of family photos mostly from the summer of 1985, with DR, PR, their children, their children's spouses, and grandchildren. Many images are in Maine, and some are of sailing trips.
  39 images
- Eastern Europe Trip for Chase Manhattan Bank, 1973 February; Black-and-white images.; Most of the images are fair to poor quality. (Box 131)
  DR's Chase Manhattan Bank trip to Hungary, Yugoslavia, Romania, and Poland. PR joined him. He had a meeting with head of state Nicolae Ceausescu while in Romania.
  54 images.
- Trip to England, Scotland, and France, 1961; Some black-and-white images. (Box 132)
  Family trip to England, Scotland, and France.
- Alaska Trip, 1991, Part 1, Color and black-and-white images. (Box 133)
  DR and PR sailing trip to Alaska with family.
- Alaska Trip, 1991, Part 2 (Box 134)
  68 images.
- Americas Society Trip to Canada, 1993 (Box 135)
  DR trip to Canada for Americas Society event.
  120 images
- Japan Trip, 1972 June; Black-and-white images. (Box 136)
  DR trip to Japan, possibly for Chase Manhattan Bank.
- Chichen Itza, Mexico, Trip Part 2, 1985 (Box 137)
  DR trip for Chase Manhattan Bank to Chichen Izta, Mexico. Images show the group touring various pyramid and temple sites.
  60 images
- Chile and Paris Trip, 2003 (Box 138)
  Two DR trips: Chile flightseeing tour in the Chilean mountains, and a book-signing event for "Memoirs" in Paris in October.
- Donald Homer Sr. Compilation Album, Hudson Pines, 2010; Photo quality varies. Some images are pixelated. (Box 139)
  Hudson Pines Farm general manager Donald Homer compiled these images of his family and his work with the cattle on Hudson Pines Farm. Images include DR, PR, and Martha Stewart. Cattle auction brochures.
- Compilation Album of DR Visits to World Markets, 1983 and 1997 (Box 140)
  DR visted marketplaces including in Peru and Morocco. PR and Bob and Linda Douglass joined him in Morocco.
- Hadrian Award Luncheon, World Monuments Fund, 1994; Black-and-white images. (Box 141)
  DR received the annual World Monuments Fund's Hadrian Award for efforts toward saving cultural heritage. Attendees included PR, Robert Douglass, Patricia and Gustavo Cisneros, and Brooke Astor (also a Hadrian recipient).
- Koc Holdings Board Dinner for Council on Foreign Relations, 1999 October 20 (Box 142)
  DR trip to Turkey for dinner held by Rahmi Koc in honor of DR and members of the U.S. Council on Foreign Relations. Held at the Rahmi Koc Museum, a private industrial museum in Istanbul.
- Merida, Venezuela Trip, 1989 (Box 143)
  DR and PR trip to Merida and surrounding area in Venezuela on behalf of Chase Manhattan Bank.
- Nancy Kissinger Birthday Celebration, 1997 (Box 144)
  DR attended a birthday celebration for Nancy Kissinger. Other guests included Henry Kissinger, Barbara Walters, Annette De la Renta, and Brooke Astor.
  40 images.